[
  {
    "question": "1 x 10",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 10",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 10",
    "options": ["20", "30", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 10",
    "options": ["30", "40", "50"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 10",
    "options": ["40", "50", "60"],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 10",
    "options": ["50", "60", "70"],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 10",
    "options": ["60", "70", "80"],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 10",
    "options": ["70", "80", "90"],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 10",
    "options": ["80", "90", "100"],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 10",
    "options": ["90", "100", "110"],
    "correctAnswer": "100"
  }
]
